Guide to the Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Collection 1938-[1970-1998] 2000
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Series VI: Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Central Records Library
  - Sub-series 1: Central Records Library
    - CRL 28032 Employee Handbook. Trust Policies and Procedures 1989-1997, 3 folders (Box 115)
    - CRL 28033 Legal Dept. Policies and Procedures Manuals 1991-1992, 3 folders (Box 115)
    - CRL 28034 Procedures for Numbering Procedures 1992-1993 (Box 116)
    - CRL 28035 Claims Processing Procedures 1992, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - CRL 28036 [Holdback and Interest, Memoranda] 1992-1993 (Box 116)
    - CRL 28037 Document Retention Policy for Breland 1994-1995 (Box 116)
    - CRL 28038 Administrative Review Team Procedures. ART/Option 3 Training 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 116-117)
    - CRL 28039 Option 3 Evaluation Rules; Claims Review Department EPR Manual 1990-1994, 7 folders (Box 117-118)
    - CRL 28040 Option 3 Claims Valuation Procedures 1990-1991, 1995, 4 folders (Box 118)
    - CRL 28041 Option 3 Factors 1990-1991, 4 folders (Box 118a)
    - CRL 28041 Option 3 Factors Book 1991, 1993 (Box 119)
    - CRL 28044 Claims Medical Resources List n.d., 2 folders (Box 119)
    - CRL 28046 Special Problems Policy and Procedures Manual 1990, 1992, 3 folders (Box 119)
    - CRL 28047 Alternative Dispute Resolution Advocate; ADR Department Policy and Procedures Manual 1992-1994, 6 folders (Box 119-120)
    - CRL 28048 ADR Dept. Training Manual n.d., 5 folders (Box 120-121)
    - CRL 28049 Breland Phone Scripts [1992-1994] (Box 121)
    - CRL 28050 MIS [Management Information Systems] Procedures 1989-1990 (Box 121)
    - CRL 28052 Claims Departmental Procedures 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 121-122)
    - CRL 28054 Option 2 Claims Review Rules and Factors 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box 122)
    - CRL 28055 LDS File Audit Procedures n.d. (Box 122)
    - CRL 28056 Fileroom Procedures n.d. (Box 122)
    - CRL 28057 Procedures for Dismantling the Gray Folders 1990-1993 (Box 122)
    - CRL 28058 General Filing Procedures for SC Files 1995 (Box 122)
    - CRL 28059 Procedures and Approval to Shred Merged Claim Files 1992, 1994 (Box 122)
    - CRL 28060 LAMS [Litigation and Arbitration Management System] User Manual 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 121-122)
    - CRL 28061 Legal Area Jobs Procedure Handbook 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 123)
    - CRL 28062 Oracle Letter Listing 1995-1996 (Box 123)
    - CRL 28063 Manual Scheduling of Payments Procedures 1996 (Box 123)
    - CRL 28064 Review of Claims to Received Warning of Rolling Complaint Deadline Procedures 1995 (Box 123)
    - CRL 28068 Procedures for Handling Requests for Reinstatement 1995 (Box 123)
    - CRL 28069 Procedures Manual for Case Assistants in Legal 1993-1994 (Box 123)
    - CRL 28070 Medical Training Manual for Case Assistants, Specialists, and Clerks 1993 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28071 Training Manual for Local Counsel 1993 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28073 Procedures on How to Prepare Reports on LDS Claims and Hearings on Objections to Trust Recommendations 1993 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28076 Attorney Removal Procedures 1996 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28077 Guidelines for NFC [Narrative Flow Chart Team] Cases 1996 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28078 Procedures for the Conversion of LAMS Claims to ADR 1995 (Box 124)
    - CRL 28080 SC Memoranda 1992-1996, 4 folders (Box 124)
    - CRL 28082 Legal Department Introduction Manual 1991-1992 (Box 125)
    - CRL 28085 Procedures for Processing Breland Legal Expenses 1996 (Box 125)
    - CRL 28086 Payment Processing Procedures 1996 (Box 125)
    - CRL 28087 Claims Complications Assessment/Valuation Process 1991-1993 (Box 125)
    - CRL 28088 Evaluation Guidelines for Determination of Window Claims and Claims Reference File 1990-1994, 8 folders (Box 125-126)
    - CRL 28089 Child Reference File 1990-1994, 14 folders (Box 126-129)
    - CRL 28090 Medical Expert Information 1991-1992 (Box 129)
    - CRL 28091 Child Claim Evaluation/Valuation 1991-1993, 4 folders (Box 129-130)
    - CRL 28092 Procedures to Address Non-Compliance Issues Relative to Atty. Fees from Pro Rata 1997 (Box 130)
    - CRL 28098 Performance Based Compensation (PBC) Graphs n.d., 2 folders (Box 130)
    - CRL 28099 Claim Disjoin Policy 1994 (Box 130)
    - CRL 28100 Severance Policy 1998 (Box 130)
    - CRL 28101 Process for Reclassifying Late Claims to Timely 1995 (Box 130)
    - CRL 28102 Investment Policy 1989-1990; 1993-1996 (Box 130)
    - CRL 29000 Inventory of Boxes Received from McGuire, Woods and Battle Law Firm 1988 (Box 131)
    - CRL 29001 Pro Rata Planning and Development of the Payment of the Pro Rata Distribution 1995, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - CRL 29004 Trust History 1985-1994, 10 folders (Box 131-132)
    - CRL 29005 NFC [Narrative Flow Chart] Development 1993-1995, 8 folders (Box 132-133)
    - CRL 29006 Discontinuation of the Claims Audit Process 1995 (Box 133)
    - CRL 29007 Project File for the Development of the 7/1/96 Mailing 1996 (Box 133)
    - CRL 29008 Project File for the Development of the FDR Mailing that Occurred on 6/1/95 1995 (Box 133)
    - CRL 29009 Legal Process Assessment Project 1995 (Box 133)
    - CRL 29011 Cost Comparison with DSCT and Manville Trust 1994-1995 (Box 134)
    - CRL 29012 Mass Mailing Team Minutes 1994 (Box 134)
    - CRL 29013 Pro Rata II Planning 1995-1996, 6 folders (Box 134)
    - CRL 29014 Option File Work 1988-1989, 5 folders (Box 134)
    - CRL 29015 Request for Proposal for Banking Services 1997, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - CRL 29019 Planning Team Project File 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - CRL 29022 Supoena Team Development Project 1995-1996 (Box 135-136)
    - CRL 29023 Oracle Address Updates 1989 (Oversize Boxes 146-147)
    - CRL 29024 Task Force for Special Mailings n.d., 2 folders (Box 136)
    - CRL 29027 Attorneys Pro Rata Fees Compliance Audit 1995-1997, 10 folders (Box 136-138)
    - CRL 31001-31016 FDR [Final Dispute Resolution] Packets 1995, 16 folders (Box 139-140)
    - [no CRL number]Attorney evaluation project 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 140-141)
    - [no CRL number]DSCT downsizing 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 142)
    - [no CRL number] Doctors addresses n.d. (Box 143-145)
    - Training Procedure and Policy Manuals (16) concerning claims evaluations, Option 3, mailings, legal issues, ADR and other topics early 1990s (Box 148-150)